​​​ ​Chat​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm actually​ ​​
​​​ ​uploading​ ​​
​​​ ​to my​ ​​
​​​ ​second channel​ ​​
​​​ ​Wow, look at that​ ​​
​​​ ​Anyways,​ ​​
​​​ ​this is a test​ ​​
​​​ ​to see how​ ​​
​​​ ​.ASS​ ​​
​​​ ​subtitles work​ ​​
​​​ ​on YouTube​ ​​
​​​ ​because I was like;​ ​​
​​​ ​“Huh, what if I could”​ ​​
​​​ ​make subtitles​ ​​
​​​ ​that had​ ​​
​​​ ​the Minecraft font?​ ​​
​​​ ​So that's what​ ​​
​​​ ​this test​ ​​
​​​ ​is gonna be​ ​​
​​​ ​So if you​ ​​
​​​ ​watch this video,​ ​​
​​​ ​uhhh-​ ​​
​​​ ​enable​ ​​
​​​ ​✨ subtitles ✨​ ​​
​​​ ​because​ ​​
​​​ ​uhh...​ ​​
​​​ ​yeah-​ ​​
​​​ ​I should​ ​​
​​​ ​probably say​ ​​
​​​ ​that at​ ​​
​​​ ​the beginning​ ​​
​​​ ​now shouldn’t I?​ ​​
​​​ ​Nawww, it's fine​ ​​
​​​ ​anyways, yeah​ ​​
​​​ ​uh that-​ ​​
​​​ ​that-​ ​​
​​​ ​that's the video.​ ​​
​​​ ​ummm​ ​​
​​​ ​Enjoy.​ ​​
​​​ ​Enjoy-​ ​​
​​​ ​re-​ ​​
​​​ ​Rewatch it​ ​​
​​​ ​with subtitles,​ ​​
​​​ ​I guess.​ ​​
​​​ ​Enjoy.​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, I​ ​​
​​​ ​forgot to​ ​​
​​​ ​stop recording.​ ​​
​​​ ​I forgot to​ ​​
​​​ ​mention this​ ​​
​​​ ​good thing​ ​​
​​​ ​I haven't posted​ ​​
​​​ ​the video yet.​ ​​
​​​ ​Um-​ ​​
​​​ ​It can also-​ ​​
​​​ ​the- sub-​ ​​
​​​ ​the-​ ​​
​​​ ​.ASS subtitles​ ​​
​​​ ​So you can also​ ​​
​​​ ​do-​ ​​
​​​ ​uh-​ ​​
​​​ ​♪ karaoke ♪​ ​​
​​​ ​So if I'm like​ ​​
​​​ ​♪ to you~ ♪​ ​​
​​​ ​♪ yes my love to you~ ♪​ ​​
​​​ ​wow amazing​ ​​
​​​ ​karaoke skills.​ ​​
​​​ ​Anyways, if you​ ​​
​​​ ​had subtitles​ ​​
​​​ ​on there.​ ​​
​​​ ​uh- It would do​ ​​
​​​ ​♪ funny stuff. ♪​ ​​
​​​ ​So. Yeah.​ ​​
​​​ ​There you go.​ ​​
​​​ ​Anyways.​ ​​
​​​ ​.ASS subtitles are very peak :D​ ​​